uppsite.com 2013-04-24

# UppSite | Privacy Policy

Last Updated: June 1, 2011

[www.uppsite.com](https://www.uppsite.com/) (the “Web Site”) is owned and operated by MySiteApp Ltd.  
The terms “MySiteApp”, “we”, “us”, “our” and “ours” when used in this Privacy Policy mean MySiteApp Ltd. which includes all its parents, subsidiaries, divisions, branches, and affiliates.  
The terms “you”, “your” and “yours” when used in this Privacy Policy means any user of the Web Site. The term “Personal Data” refers to personally identifiable information about you, such as your name, birth date, cell phone number, e-mail address or mailing address. The term “App” when used in this Privacy Policy means an application for mobile devices, which is generated through the use of the Web Site.  
This Privacy Policy describes MySiteApp’s current policies and practices with regard to Personal Data collected by MySiteApp through the Web Site. 

Acceptance

By accessing, browsing, submitting information to, or other use of the, Web Site you are agreeing to this Privacy Policy. You may not use the Web Site or submit any information to MySiteApp if you do not agree to any of the terms herein. 

Collection of Personal Data Including E-Mail Addresses

MySiteApp takes your privacy seriously.  We respect and protect the privacy of our users and take appropriate steps to safeguard your personal information.  
We collect the information you give us when you visit our Web Site and use it when you request to be contacted. You may, through the Web Site, register to receive additional information (e.g. newsletters) from us, or to use one of our services now or in the future (e.g. uploading content and using our services). When you register, we may ask you for contact information like your name, postal address and e-mail address.  
We sometimes supplement the information that you provide with information that is received from third parties. For instance, if inaccurate postal or zip codes are received, we will use third party software to fix them.  

MySiteApp Email Marketing Communication Policy

MySiteApp sends promotional email only to: 

  * Customers
  * People who have given consent to MySiteApp to receive promotional email
  * People on rented email lists who have given permission to the list owner to receive third-party promotional email
  * All of the abovementioned who have not opted out after having received promotional email from us.

In each promotional email, we include an easy and clear way to opt out of future MySiteApp email. Opt-out requests are submitted through [Support@MySiteapp.com](mailto:Support@MySiteapp.com), and such Opt-out requests are processed within 10 business days. When sending email to rented email lists, we suppress addresses of those people who have opted out of MySiteApp email in the past.  
We always disclose our identity in mass email communications, including the address of our headquarters location.  
We never use deceiving header information or subject lines.  
We never send mass, promotional email to email addresses “harvested” from websites.  
We never, under any circumstances, rent or sell email addresses to any other company or individual.  
When coordinating with our resellers for the purpose of follow-up on sales inquiries made to us, we provide full contact information of the inquirer to the reseller, including email address, so the reseller can follow up on the inquiry. 

Our marketing email policy and practice fully conforms to the United States Federal “CAN SPAM” act of 2003 and the applicable Israeli statues such as the Protection of Privacy Law 5741-1981.  Note that some regions such as the European Union, have different email laws and guidelines, and MySiteApp conforms to local laws in those cases. We welcome and encourage your thoughts on this policy at [Support@MySiteapp.com](mailto:Support@MySiteapp.com). 

User Communications

When you send email or other communication to MySiteApp, we may retain those communications in order to process your inquiries, respond to your requests and improve our services. 

Use of Personal Data

We process your Personal Data to try to provide a safe, efficient, and customized experience, and only for specific and limited purposes. We ask only for data that is adequate, relevant and not excessive for those purposes. When we ask you for Personal Data, we tell you the purposes for which we will process that data.  
Some of these purposes include the following: 

  * We may contact you occasionally to inform you of new services we will be providing, or special offers, events or articles we think will be of interest to you.
  * We may send you regular updates by e-mail on MySiteApp organized or related events.
  * We may send you requested product information and promotional material.
  * We may use your Personal Data for marketing purposes and market research.
  * We may use your Personal Data internally to help us improve our products and services and to help resolve any problems.

Disclosure of Your Personal Data

We do not share, sell or distribute your Personal Data with unrelated third parties, except under these limited circumstances: 

  * **Business:** Personal Data may occasionally be transferred to third parties who act for or on behalf of MySiteApp, or in connection with the business of MySiteApp for further processing in accordance with the purposes for which the data was originally collected or for purposes to which you have subsequently consented. For example, sometimes a third party may have access to your Personal Data in order to handle our mailings on our behalf.
  * **Billing:** Personal Data may also be shared with certain third parties we use to perform functions such as billing and cellular services.  We cannot assure that these third parties will treat your information in accordance with this Privacy Policy.
  * **Stores:** Personal Data may be shared with moderators and regulators, such as the Apple App Store or Google’s Android Market, in order to upload your MySiteApp app to such sites.We may share or transfer the information in our databases to comply with a legal requirement, for the administration of justice, to protect your vital interests, to protect the security or integrity of our databases or this Web Site, to take precautions against legal liability, or in the event of a corporate sale, merger, reorganization, dissolution or similar event.
  * **Disclosing:** Where appropriate, before disclosing Personal Data to a third party, we contractually require the third party to take adequate precautions to protect that data.

Anonymous Data Collected Through This Web Site

In addition to the information we collect as described above, we use technology to collect anonymous information about the use of our Web Site and any application created using our Web Site. This technology does not identify you personally; it simply enables us to compile statistics about our visitors and their use of our Web Site. The statistical information may be transmitted to third party sites which then use it to custom tailor media sent by them through the App.We also use this anonymous data to improve the content and functionality of this Web Site, the App and our e-mail updates, to better understand our customers and markets, and to improve our products and services. 

Cookies

  * **What is a cookie:** In order to collect the anonymous data described in the preceding paragraph, we may use “cookies” that collect the first level domain name of the user and the date and time you accessed this Web Site.  A cookie is a small file containing a string of characters. This information is sent to your computer when you use the Web Site and it’s stored on your computer, subject to your cookies storage preferences, so that we can uniquely identify a user’s browser.
  * **Diagnose Problems:** We also use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our Web Site. An IP address is a numeric code that identifies your computer on a network, or in this case, the Internet. Your IP address is also used to gather broad demographic information, such as determining the geographical regions of our visitors and users.
  * **Advertising:** We may also use cookies and similar tools to customize the content and advertising you receive based on the Personal Data you have provided.  Personal Data you provide in structured profile fields or questions, information you add to open-ended profile fields and questions and other information about you may also be used to customize the online ads you encounter to those we believe are aligned with your interests.  The information used for this feature does not provide your personal information or identify you as an individual to third parties.

Third-Party Sites

Since the App interfaces with third-party sites for advertising purposes, you and the users of your App may be sending certain information to third parties which may reveal usage statistics and other information to such third-parties. It is your responsibility to read and understand their terms of use, privacy policy and any other instructions published by such sites prior to using the App. We will not be responsible for the policies or conduct of any third-party sites. 

Links to Other Web Sites

This Privacy Policy applies only to www.uppsite.com and to other MySiteApp URLs through or from which you have reached this Web Site. This Web Site contains hyperlinks to web sites that are not operated by MySiteApp. These hyperlinks are provided for your reference and convenience only and do not imply any endorsement of the activities of these third-party web sites or any association with their operators. We do not control these web sites and are not responsible for their data collection or privacy practices. We urge you to review any privacy policy posted on any site you visit before using the site or providing any Personal Data about yourself. 

Information Security

We take appropriate security measures to protect against unauthorized access to or unauthorized alteration, disclosure or destruction of data. These include internal reviews of our data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures, as well as physical security measures to guard against unauthorized access to systems where we store personal data.Access to Personal Data is for restricted to designated MySiteApp employees, contractors and agents who need to know that information in order to operate, develop or improve our services. These individuals are bound by confidentiality obligations and may be subject to discipline, including termination and criminal prosecution, if they fail to meet these obligations. 

Transfer of Data Abroad

MySiteApp is a web-based global enterprise and has facilities and databases in different countries. We may, from time to time, transfer your Personal Data to one of our databases in another country. If the level of privacy protection in a country does not comply with recognized international standards, we will ensure that data transferred to our databases in that country are adequately protected and that the transfer of data to third parties in such countries is made pursuant to a contract or other measures providing adequate protection.Of course, the Internet is made up of a large number of international connections. If you are visiting this Web Site from a country other than the country in which our server is located, the various communications will necessarily result in the transfer of information across international boundaries. By visiting this Web Site and communicating electronically with us, you consent to these transfers. 

Special Note for Parents and Children Under Age 18

The site you are visiting is a general audience site. The Web Site is not directed to persons under 18. If a parent or guardian becomes aware that his or her child has provided us with personal information without their consent, he or she should contact us. We do not knowingly collect or solicit personal information from people under 18. If we become aware that a person under 18 has provided us with personal information, we will delete such information from our files.We recommend that minors over the age of 13 ask their parents or guardian for permission before sending any information about themselves to anyone over the internet. 

Changes to This Policy

This Policy may change from time to time. We will post any Policy changes on this page and, if the changes are significant, we will provide a more prominent notice. You are encouraged to check for the latest Policy as often as you wish. Each version of this Policy will be identified at the top of the page by its effective date, and we will also keep prior versions of this Policy in an archive for your review. 

Questions

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or concerns about the way we process your Personal Data, please contact us by e-mailing us at [Support@MySiteapp.com](mailto:Support@MySiteapp.com)
